do today's short video so that I can
later talk on camera and do a long long
video that I am then gonna edit to
explain my idea the important parts of
it and then actually share it on my
Facebook group like my Facebook and look
my business project 1 crowd democracy
and my personal one
so that's scary for me and but I know
until I stuck into my power this isn't
gonna go anywhere until I'm comfortable
expressing this idea to people that I
know and that know me I it's not gonna
go anywhere
so that's what I will be doing I won't
be doing it today but I'll be recording
the video part of it today and then
actually learning how to edit it and
putting you out there for the world to
see I did a fairly decent video
yesterday I contained recording
afterwards oh so I'm not gonna post at
the moment that would also take video
editing where I just let go of my story
of that I don't know how to do this and
was like just do it just do it and I did
a fairly good job in under it was like
six seven minutes explaining what I'm
here to put on this planet to do and the
lie of it and so I'm pretty sure I can
do it I can sit here and talk about it
and edit that video but today's video
isn't that because I can't do it in a
minute video and I've committed to
posting a video every day so today's
video will be this video so we made it
in hit 30 seconds so make it longer
we'll just post this one how to change
the world how do start a global
cooperative I don't know how but I'm
looking for people
I want people I want to collab
collaboration that doesn't need a co in
front of it or you got a co because it's
already together
I want to collaborate with people I want
to meet and decide on courses of action
which are not my best my strong point
but I know other people know how to do
that and that I can take the action
if someone else is like do this exact
thing I can do it so we can split up the
work and share the vision create the
vision together create a shared vision
together figure out where we are where
we need to be in the steps needed to get
there and just start taking them but I
don't want to do it alone I know very
strongly that I'm not the person to do
this by myself I physically just can't
can't do all of the work and although
other people told me I have to be the
person I have to be the one in charge I
don't want to be and I'm not going to be
there's something in me that says that's
not how this is done this is done
through collaboration through people who
share is Colleen to make knowledge
accessible to everyone and don't have a
hierarchy of knowledge and all of the
power that that gives the people and all
the possibility it gives humanity I just
have to express that to the world
be in the moment be my true self and
explain why this needs to happen and the
right people will come on board at the
right time and until that happens I'm
doing this I'm putting up videos but
you're how to edit them which is
something that is is a sticking point
from you for sure and I'm just going to
show up being me because I'm the one who
you know there's no one else who that I
know that has an actual solution to the
problems on the planet that we can all
participate in otherwise I'll join them
and be on board with them but this
doesn't exist pieces of it exist and I
think we can do better when we
collectively own those pieces but it
doesn't exist or I'd be part of it or if
it does exist
show me where it is and I will join it
all right that was today's video I hope
the title is gonna be because it's
pretty pretty all over the place but
it'll be coming I'm going to be posting
and
video that I've edited edited down from
however long I need to sit and talk
about the global cooperative to feel
like I've done it justice I'm just ready
I'm ready for this I've been ready for a
while but I'm ready for it to actually
start to actually plan a weekly meeting
to discuss where we are and where we
need to go and have people on board
I woke up this epiphany yesterday that
like I actually do need to invite people
as I find people that I want to
collaborate with I have to invite them
and not just be like hey do you think
maybe you know someone who might be
interested like are you interested and
yeah that's pretty parallels in my
dating life I think I need to actually
ask and it's terrifying and I love that